<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Gabriel Vera</title>
    <link>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Gabriel Vera</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leet Code</title>
      <link>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/project/leet_code/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/project/leet_code/</guid>
      <description>I was recently introduced to Leet Code by a colleague and have taken a liking to it.
Upon some further research I have learned that is is very prominent for companies to take problems from these in coding interviews. That in combination with the fact that I am trying to learn more languages made me want to try it.
It&amp;rsquo;s still a work in progress, but I will post solutions as I go through them in various languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Euler</title>
      <link>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/project/project_euler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/project/project_euler/</guid>
      <description>A current ongoing project that has piqued my interest is Project Euler . Essentially it&amp;rsquo;s a series of math problems for which you need to devise an algorithm and a program to compute the solution.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it as a way to ramp up my skills in other languages that I am not comfortable with such as, Perl 6 , Clojure , and Ruby . I chose these languages for different reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website</title>
      <link>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/project/website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/project/website/</guid>
      <description>This website is my biggest personal project that I have undertaken.
It is hosted with Github Pages , which by far was the best option for my purpose. I wanted to have a website where I could showcase some projects that would show my skills and what tools and languages I am currently looking at.
As Github pages only hosts static sites I had to find the best tool to generate a static site that was presentable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>