<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Schools on Gabriel Vera</title>
    <link>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/school/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Schools on Gabriel Vera</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/school/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Arizona State University</title>
      <link>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/school/asu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/school/asu/</guid>
      <description>I transferred to Arizona State University in Fall of 2015. I picked ASU over a couple schools that I had gotten into including UCSD and UCSC. ASU was certainly a huge change from SCC escpecially since I had moved here from California and it was the first time I had been away from my family. However, I did come here with my best friend from high school so that definitely made the process easier for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Santiago Canyon College</title>
      <link>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/school/santiago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/school/santiago/</guid>
      <description>I went to Santiago Canyon College for 3 years after getting out of high school. Getting the classes I needed to transfer proved difficult given the volume of students that attended.
One of the major difficulties I had was getting into the programming and physics classes that were required to transer. There was only one professor at the time teaching C++ class required to transer, and his class filled up really quick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Esperanza High School</title>
      <link>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/school/esperanza/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gabrieljosephvera.com/school/esperanza/</guid>
      <description>I went to Esperanza from Fall 2008 to Spring 2012. My first experience of high school was joining the football team, and meeting many new people.
School went pretty well, but was fairly challenging due to the amount of time that was required from football. Over time I realized the sport wasn&amp;rsquo;t for me. Not due to the challenge of the sport, but just didn&amp;rsquo;t really fit for me.
After my last season of football my sophomore year I joined the track team.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>